https://www.copleyscientific.com/about/privacy-policy/

Inhaler TestingDelivered Dose Uniformity (DDU)Metered Dose InhalersDry Powder Inhalers (DPIs)NebulisersAqueous Droplet Inhalers (ADIs)Nasal ProductsAerodynamic Particle Size Distribution (APSD)Metered Dose InhalersDry Powder Inhalers (DPIs)NebulisersAqueous Droplet Inhalers (ADIs)Nasal ProductsAncillariesBreathing SimulatorsCritical Flow and Breath Actuation ControlFlow MetersMouthpiece AdaptersVacuum PumpsCITDASLabour Saving ToolsLabour Saving Tools for DDULabour Saving Tools for APSDSemi-Automation – Shake & Fire Systems for MDIsSpecial ApplicationsAbbreviated Impactor Measurement (AIM)USP Monographs (Generic Drug Development)Cold Freon® EffectIVIVCInhaled DissolutionFacemask TestingPharmaceutical TestingTablet Disintegration TestingDTGi SeriesTablet Dissolution TestingDISi SeriesTablet Friability TestingFriabimat: Coated TabletsFRVi Series: Uncoated TabletsTablet Hardness Testing (Breaking Force)Tablet Hardness Tester: TBF 100iTablet Hardness Tester: TH3Powder TestingTapped Density: JVi SeriesBulk Density: Scott VolumeterFlowability: BEP2Semisolids TestingVertical Diffusion Cell Test System: HDT 1000Vertical Diffusion Cell Test System: HDT 1Suppository TestingVaginal Tablet Tester: VTTSuppository Disintegration Testing: SDT 1000Tablet Thickness TestingTablet Thickness Tester 547Tablet Thickness Tester 700Digital Caliper Model 500Detergent TestingTergotometerTergotometer: TRG 800iResourcesTrainingServicingSupportDownloadsNews & EventsAbout UsOur HistoryFaces of CopleyCareersContactContact UsOffices and Distributors
Go BackPrivacy PolicyThe purpose of this policy is to set out how we collect personal information for you, how we process and use it, and how we will protect it. By visiting our website you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy.In this privacy policy (Privacy Policy), ‘Company’, ‘we’ or ‘us’ refers to the following company: Copley Scientific Limited. The company supplies laboratory equipment for the testing of inhalers and solid dosage forms. The activities undertaken to enable this to happen are collectively referred to in this Privacy Policy as ‘Company activities’.For the purposes of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) the data controller is Copley Scientific Limited (a company registered in England and Wales, whose registered office is at Colwick Quays Business Park, Private Road No. 2, Colwick, Nottingham, NG4 2JY, United Kingdom, company number 1390012 and VAT Number GB 309 3977 30).We take the security of your information very seriously and we endeavour to take all reasonable steps to protect your personal information. However, we cannot guarantee the security of any data you disclose on-line. You accept the inherent security risks of providing information and dealing on-line over the Internet and will not hold us responsible for any breach of security unless this is due to our negligence or wilful defaultBy submitting your details, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as set out in this Privacy Policy. We will not disclose your details to third parties (unrelated to Company activities) for the purposes of marketing. If you do not agree with the terms set out herein, please do not visit this website. Your Personal InformationWhen you contact us for information about Company activities, request a quote, place an order, make a complaint or use this website we may collect data from you. This includes:your name, company name, address and other contact details;profile or preferences you provide to us;details of transactions that you wish to conclude through this website;credit card or other payment details; and/ordetails of your visit to this website including but not limited to, traffic data, location data and the resources that you access.Information that you give us may be supplemented with information available to us from other sources such as address checking services, screening data against preference services, and standard industry classification information for profiling purposes. How we use your informationWe may use the information you give us for the following purposes:to perform legitimate business activities including preparing quotations and fulfilling ordersto communicate with you about services and information that you have requested about Company products and activitiesfor assessment and analysis (e.g. market, customer, information and product analysis) to enable us to review, develop and improve the products and services which we offer and to enable us to provide you with information we believe will closely match your preferences;to notify you of changes to the Company activities;for legitimate business record keeping purposes. Disclosure of Your InformationWe may give information about you to the following, who may use it for the same purposes as set out above:to our partners and third parties that collaborate with usagents and third parties who fulfill any other services on Company’s behalfto anyone to whom we transfer or may transfer our rights and duties with you (for example a sale of the business)if we have a duty to do so or if the law allows us to do so.In carrying out the activities specified in this Privacy Policy, we may transfer data to reputable companies outside the European Economic Area. We take steps to ensure that your information will be afforded the same level of protection as that required of us under applicable UK data protection legislation. By submitting your personal data you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. Protecting Your Personal InformationCopley Scientific Ltd is committed to protecting the data you share with us. We have put in place security measures in place to prevent your personal data being accidently lost, used or accessed in an unauthorised way. We limit access to your personal data to those employees, agents and other third parties who have a business need to know. We have put in place procedures to deal with any suspected personal data breach and will notify you and any acceptable regulatory authorities of a breach where we are legally obliged to do so.All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Retention and Deletion of Personal DataCopley Scientific Ltd will not retain data longer than is necessary to fulfil the purposes for which it was collected or as required by applicable laws or regulations. What to do if you do not want to receive information about the Company?If you prefer not to receive details of offers, products and services from us, you can opt out at any time by writing to us by mail or email (see the section “How to Contact Us” below).Please note, if you do opt out of receiving information, we will be unable to keep you informed of new services, products or events that may interest you and you will no longer be eligible for free content.Our website may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these sites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites. CookiesIn common with many other website operators, we may use standard technology called ‘cookies’ on this website. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive and they are used to record how you navigate this website on each visit.Our cookies are used to enable us to develop our website to reflect our users’ interests and by noting who has seen which pages, how frequently particular pages are visited and determining the most popular areas of our website. We may use cookies to improve your use of the website by allowing us to tailor what you see to what we have learned about your preferences during your visits to the website.Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent cookies being stored. Please note, if you do turn cookies off this will limit the service that we are able to provide to you and may affect your visitor experience.For further information on cookies and how to switch them off see: www.allaboutcookies.org. Web AnalyticsWe measure visitors to our website using Google Analytics. This records what pages you view within our site, how you arrived at our site and some basic information about your computer. The information we collect from analytics helps us understand what parts of our sites are doing well, and which need changing. Like most websites, we use this information to improve our customer experience. Please see here how Google uses data. You can also opt out if you wish. Integration of YouTube VideosWe have integrated YouTube videos into our website. The videos are stored on YouTube.com and can be played directly from our website. These are all integrated in the “extended data protection mode”, i.e. no data about you as a user will be transmitted to YouTube if you do not play the videos. Only when you play the videos will the data be transmitted. We have no influence on this data transmission. With the integration of YouTube videos, we pursue our interest in making our website more interesting and attractive for our visitors and to achieve a better presentation of contents and/or facts. YouTube is powered by Google. For more information on how YouTube handles user data, please consult the YouTube Data Privacy Policy under: policies.google.com/privacy. Your Legal RightsUnder the requirements of the General Data Protection Regulation ((EU) 2016/679) (GDPR) you have the right to see the personal data we hold on you, request that we amend, correct or delete it. You may do this by contacting us directly.Please be aware that our website may link to other websites which may be accessed through our website. We are not responsible for the data policies or procedures or the content of these linked websites.In order to protect you, our customers and us from fraud, we may use and disclose or verify information that we obtain from making identity checks and other information in our customer records, for the purposes of fraud prevention and detection.Any changes we make to this Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by email. How to contact usIf you would like to request, amend or delete the personal information we have about you, change your preferences or require further information, have any comments or questions about our Privacy Policy or any other aspect of our website, please contact us:Data Privacy Manager, Copley Scientific Limited Colwick Quays Business Park, Private Road No. 2, Colwick, Nottingham, NG4 2JY, United Kingdom, or by sending an email to privacy@copleyscientific.co.uk
Contact Us TodayHave a question? Our friendly and experienced team are here to help.
T: +44 (0)115 961 6229
E: sales@copleyscientific.co.ukFooter Form
Full Name
*
Email Address
*
Institution/Company Name
*
Virgin Islands, British
Virgin Islands, U.S.
Yemen
Zambia
Zimbabwe
Service Type
*
Interest Area
Inhaler Testing
Pharmaceutical Testing
Detergent Testing
Other
iMessage
*
We would like to keep you informed with the latest news, innovations and product information from Copley Scientific. Please let us know if you would like us to contact you or not by selecting one of the options below.
*
Yes please, I would like to stay up to date with the latest news, innovations and product information from Copley.
No thanks, I don't want to hear the latest news, innovations and product information from Copley.
Please review our privacy policy so you understand how we collect and use your personal data.
reCAPTCHA
Send Enquiry
If you are human, leave this field blank.
We use cookies on our website to give you the most relevant experience by remembering your preferences and repeat visits. By clicking “Accept”, you consent to the use of ALL the cookies.Cookie settingsACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy OverviewThis website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always EnabledNecessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessaryAny cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
X
Coronavirus – The latest update from Copley Scientific –
Find Out More
